Amanda Steele Show.
What should we remove or prohibit from Florida?
Because Florida continues to flex its racist redneck muscles
and say, yo, we don't like y'all.
Because I think a lot of folks feel like
when they hear these things,
it don't got nothing to do with them
or they think like it can't be stopped.
It can't be challenged.
It can't be dealt with.
And I'm just like,
do you understand that people like,
escape from a slave plantations?
We could figure out how to not have Florida be popping.
You know what I'm saying?
Like challenge ourselves, challenge ourselves.
I think that black athletes
shouldn't play for Florida colleges.
Like imagine if black athletes were like,
nah, we're not going to University of Miami.
We're not going to FSU.
We're not going to UF.
Like unless it's an HBCU, we're not going.
That would change things in like a real way.
I feel like it's very important that
we understand that there's like other options.
We are, we are, we are.